[
    {
        "question": "Q1: Who developed jQuery, and in which year it was first released?",
        "a":"John Richard in 2001",
        "b":"Mark Bensman in 2004",
        "c":"John Resig in 2006",
        "d":"None of the above",
        "ans":"ans3"
    },
    {
        "question": "Q2: jQuery is a -",
        "a":"JavaScript method",
        "b":"JavaScript library",
        "c":"JSON library",
        "d":"PHP method",
        "ans":"ans2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Q3: Which of the following sign is used as a shortcut for jQuery?",
        "a":"the % sign",
        "b":"the & sign",
        "c":"the $ sign",
        "d":"the @ sign",
        "ans":"ans3"
    },
    {
        "question": "Q4: $(this) in jQuery is used when -",
        "a":"an HTML element references the entire document",
        "b":"an HTML element references its own action",
        "c":"an HTML element references the action of its parent element",
        "d":"All of the above",
        "ans":"ans2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Q5: Which of the following jQuery method is used to hide the selected elements?",
        "a":"The hidden() method",
        "b":"The hide() method",
        "c":"The visible(false) method",
        "d":"The display(none) method",
        "ans":"ans2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Q6: Which jQuery method is used to set one or more style properties to the selected element?",
        "a":"The html() method",
        "b":"The style() method",
        "c":"The css() method",
        "d":"All of the above",
        "ans":"ans3"
    },
    {
        "question": "Q7:  Which of the following jQuery method is used to attach a handler to an event?",
        "a":"unbind() method",
        "b":"attach() method",
        "c":"bind() method",
        "d":"None of the above",
        "ans":"ans3"
    },
    {
        "question": "Q8: The jQuery method used to perform an asynchronous HTTP request -",
        "a":"jQuery ajaxSetup() method",
        "b":"jQuery ajaxSync() method",
        "c":"jQuery ajax() method",
        "d":"None of the above",
        "ans":"ans3"
    },
    {
        "question": "Q9: Which of the following jQuery method is used to stop jQuery for few milliseconds?",
        "a":"stop() method",
        "b":"delay() method",
        "c":"slowdown() method",
        "d":"pause() method",
        "ans":"ans2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Q10: Which of the jQuery function prevents the code from running before the loading of the document finishes?",
        "a":"$(document).load()",
        "b":"$(document).unload()",
        "c":"$(document).ready()",
        "d":"$(document).trim()",
        "ans":"ans3"
    }
]